Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Individuals, 1870-1972; Series I
  - Sozanski, Edward J. (Box 71, Folder 3315)
  - Spaeth, Edmund B. (Box 71, Folder 3316)
  - Sparkman, Palmer (Box 71, Folder 3317)
  - Spates, Thomas G. (Box 71, Folder 3318)
  - Spearoff, Leon (Box 71, Folder 3319)
  - Spector, Arlen (Box 71, Folder 3320)
  - Spence, Jonathan (Box 71, Folder 3321)
  - Spence, Richard P. (Box 71, Folder 3322)
  - Spender, Stephen (Box 71, Folder 3323)
  - Spiegel, Herman D. J. (Box 71, Folder 3324)
  - Spiro, Howard M. (Box 71, Folder 3325)
  - Spitzer, Charles F. (Box 71, Folder 3326)
  - Spitzer, Lymann (Box 71, Folder 3327)
  - Spofford, Charles (Box 71, Folder 3328)
  - Springer, George P. (Box 71, Folder 3329)
  - Staebler, ----- (Box 71, Folder 3330)
  - Stainbrook, Edward (Box 71, Folder 3331)
  - Stanberry, William (Box 71, Folder 3332)
  - Stancisko, Stephen (Box 72, Folder 3333)
  - Stapleton, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3334)
  - Starnes, Robert L. (Box 72, Folder 3335)
  - Starr, Mark (Box 72, Folder 3336)
  - Stathis, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3337)
  - Steadman, John M. (Box 72, Folder 3338)
  - Stebbins, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3339)
  - Stebbins, Theodore E., Jr. (Box 72, Folder 3340)
  - Stein, Howard (Box 72, Folder 3341)
  - Steinbach, Milton (Box 72, Folder 3342)
  - Steinbrunner, John (Box 72, Folder 3343)
  - Steinem, Gloria (Box 72, Folder 3344)
  - Stendal, Krister (Box 72, Folder 3345)
  - Stephen, Michael J. (Box 72, Folder 3346)
  - Stephens, Ferris J. (Box 72, Folder 3347)
  - Stephens, Shand (Box 72, Folder 3348)
  - Stern, David (Box 72, Folder 3349)
  - Stevens, Robert B. (Box 72, Folder 3350)
  - Stevens, Rosemary A. (Box 72, Folder 3351)
  - Stevens, Sheperd (Box 72, Folder 3352)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 72, Folder 3353)
  - Stevenson, Lloyd G. (Box 72, Folder 3354)
  - Steward, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3355)
  - Stewart, George (Box 72, Folder 3356)
  - Stewart, J. (Box 72, Folder 3357)
  - Stewart, Potter (Box 72, Folder 3358)
  - Stewart, Richard (Box 72, Folder 3359)
  - Stewart, Zeph (Box 72, Folder 3360)
  - Stieber, Joachim W. (Box 72, Folder 3361)
  - Stiglitz, Joseph E. (Box 72, Folder 3362)
  - Stiles, Ezra (Box 72, Folder 3363)
  - Stimson, Henry L. (Box 72, Folder 3364)
  - Stockel, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3365)
  - Stoddard, jack (Box 72, Folder 3366)
  - Stoddard, Carlos F. (Box 72, Folder 3367)
  - Stoekel, Gustave (Box 72, Folder 3368)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 72, Folder 3369)
  - Stokes, Carl B. (Box 72, Folder 3370)
  - Stokes, Jerome W. (Box 72, Folder 3371)
  - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 72, Folder 3372)
  - Stone, Albert E. (Box 72, Folder 3373)
  - Stone, Andy (Box 72, Folder 3374)
  - Stone, Edward L. (Box 72, Folder 3375)
  - Stone, Leon S. (Box 72, Folder 3376)
  - Stone, Melville E. (Box 72, Folder 3377)
  - Stone, Roger D. (Box 72, Folder 3378)
  - Stout, Edgar L. (Box 72, Folder 3379)
  - Stowe, Bruce B. (Box 72, Folder 3380)
  - Stratton, John (Box 72, Folder 3381)
  - Stratton, Julius (Box 72, Folder 3382)
  - Straus, Robert (Box 72, Folder 3383)
  - Strauss, John Steaven (Box 72, Folder 3384)
  - Street, Emeline A. (Box 72, Folder 3385)
  - Strodtbeck, Fred L. (Box 72, Folder 3386)
  - Stromquist, Shel (Box 72, Folder 3387)
  - Strong, Leonell C. (Box 72, Folder 3388)
  - Strout, ----- (Box 72, Folder 3389)
  - Stryer, Lubert (Box 72, Folder 3390)
  - Stuart, Van L. (Box 72, Folder 3391)
  - Stubbs, Frank Bernard (Box 72, Folder 3392)
  - Stuiver, Minze (Box 72, Folder 3393)
  - Sturdy, Herbert (Box 73, Folder 3394)
  - Sturges, Wesley A. (Box 73, Folder 3395)
  - Sturm, Justin (Box 73, Folder 3396)
  - Sturtevant, Julian M. (Box 73, Folder 3397)
  - Suisman, Michael (Box 73, Folder 3398)
  - Sullivan, ----- (Box 73, Folder 3399)
  - Sullivan, Don (Box 73, Folder 3400)
  - Sullivan, Edward (Box 73, Folder 3401)
  - Sullivan, Edward D. S. (Box 73, Folder 3402)
  - Sullivan, Scott G. (Box 73, Folder 3403)
  - Sullivan, Walter (Box 73, Folder 3404)
  - Sullivan, William O. (Box 73, Folder 3405)
  - Summers, Clyde W. (Box 73, Folder 3406)
  - Sumner, Duward F. (Box 73, Folder 3407)
  - Sumner, William G. (Box 73, Folder 3408)
  - Suplinskas, Raymond J. (Box 73, Folder 3409)
  - Sutro, Ogden W. (Box 73, Folder 3410)
  - Suttie, Roscoe H. (Box 73, Folder 3411)
  - Sutton, Percy (Box 73, Folder 3412)
  - Swain, Anthony (Box 73, Folder 3413)
  - Swan, Thomas W. (Box 73, Folder 3414)
  - Swanson, Maynard (Box 73, Folder 3415)
  - Sweeting, Orville J. (Box 73, Folder 3416)
  - Swenson, Edward F., Jr. (Box 73, Folder 3417)
  - Swift, Gordon C. (Box 73, Folder 3418)
  - Swift, Kate (Box 73, Folder 3419)
  - Swil (Box 73, Folder 3420)
  - Switzer, Gilbert H. (Box 73, Folder 3421)
  - Swope, J. Morgan (Box 73, Folder 3422)
  - Swords, Gerard S. (Box 73, Folder 3423)
  - Sylvester, Richard S. (Box 73, Folder 3424)
  - Symes, Ronald (Box 73, Folder 3425)
  - Symington, James W. (Box 73, Folder 3426)
  - Symington, William S. (Box 73, Folder 3427)
  - Snyder, Charles R. (Box 73, Folder 3428)
  - Szczarba, Robert H. (Box 73, Folder 3429)
  - Szebehely, Victor G. (Box 73, Folder 3430)
  - Szell, George (Box 73, Folder 3431)
  - Taffel, Max (Box 73, Folder 3432)
  - Taft, Charles Phelps (Box 73, Folder 3433)
  - Taft, Horace D. (Box 73, Folder 3434)
  - Taft, Robert (Box 73, Folder 3435)
  - Taft, William Howard (Box 73, Folder 3436)
  - Takenaka, Masao (Box 73, Folder 3437)
  - Talbott, Nelson Strobridge III (Box 73, Folder 3438)
  - Tallchief, Maria (Box 73, Folder 3439)
  - Tamagawa, Tsuneo (Box 73, Folder 3440)
  - Tanis, James R. (Box 73, Folder 3441)
  - Tarsaidze, ----- (Box 73, Folder 3442)
  - Tate, Jack B. (Box 73, Folder 3443)
  - Tath, Huot (Box 74, Folder 3444)
  - Taubman, ----- (Box 74, Folder 3445)
  - Taylor, Charles Henry (Box 74, Folder 3446)
  - Taylor, Charles Lewis (Box 74, Folder 3447)
  - Taylor, Donald W. (Box 74, Folder 3448)
  - Taylor, Lex (Box 74, Folder 3449)
  - Tedesco, Paul M. (Box 74, Folder 3450)
  - Teller, edward (Box 74, Folder 3451)
  - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth (Box 74, Folder 3452)
  - Tennant, Richard B. (Box 74, Folder 3453)
  - Tenney, James C. (Box 74, Folder 3454)
  - Terrill, James (Box 74, Folder 3455)
  - Teselle, Eugene A. (Box 74, Folder 3456)
  - Teselle, Sallie (Box 74, Folder 3457)
  - Teush, Bart F. (Box 74, Folder 3458)
  - Thayer, ----- (Box 74, Folder 3459)
  - Theiler, Max (Box 74, Folder 3460)
  - Theobald, Robert (Box 74, Folder 3461)
  - Thieme, Paul (Box 74, Folder 3462)
  - Thomas, Elizabeth (Box 74, Folder 3463)
  - Thomas, Franklin A. (Box 74, Folder 3464)
  - Thomas, Henry C. (Box 74, Folder 3465)
  - Thomas, Herbert (Box 74, Folder 3466)
  - Thomas, James A. (Box 74, Folder 3467)
  - Thomas, Jett D. (Box 74, Folder 3468)
  - Thomas, Lewis (Box 74, Folder 3469)
  - Thomas, Lowell (Box 74, Folder 3470)
  - Thomas, Norman (Box 74, Folder 3471)
  - Thompson, Ernest F. (Box 74, Folder 3472)
  - Thompson, George (Box 74, Folder 3473)
  - Thompson, John D. (Box 74, Folder 3474)
  - Thompson, John Russell (Box 74, Folder 3475)
  - Thompson, Josiah (Box 74, Folder 3476)
  - Thompson, Leonard M. (Box 74, Folder 3477)
  - Thompson, R. H. (Box 74, Folder 3478)
  - Thompson, Robert (Box 74, Folder 3479)
  - Thompson, Tim (Box 74, Folder 3480)
  - Thoms, Herbert (Box 74, Folder 3481)
  - Thomson, Keith S. (Box 74, Folder 3482)
  - Thong, Huynh Sanh (Box 74, Folder 3483)
  - Thorburn, James G., Jr. (Box 74, Folder 3484)
  - Thorn, Edwin (Box 74, Folder 3485)
  - Thorn, Mr. and Mrs. Lewis (Box 74, Folder 3486)
  - Thorne, James N. (Box 74, Folder 3487)
  - Thorne, Samuel E. (Box 74, Folder 3488)
  - Tierney, Joseph Paul (Box 74, Folder 3489)
  - Tighe, Laurence G. (Box 74, Folder 3490)
  - Tilboorg, Gregory (Box 74, Folder 3491)
  - Tillich, Paul (Box 74, Folder 3492)
  - Tilman, Robert O. (Box 74, Folder 3493)
  - Tilson, Catherine J. (Box 74, Folder 3494)
  - Tilson, John Q. (Box 75, Folder 3495)
  - Tilton, J. Warren (Box 75, Folder 3496)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B. (Box 75, Folder 3497)
  - Tinsley, Beatrice M. (Box 75, Folder 3498)
  - Tippo, Oswald (Box 75, Folder 3499)
  - Tobin, Austin J. (Box 75, Folder 3500)
  - Tobin, James (Box 75, Folder 3501)
  - Tobin, Wallace E., III (Box 75, Folder 3502)
  - Toelle, Hedwig (Box 75, Folder 3503)
  - Toland, Robert, Jr. (Box 75, Folder 3504)
  - Tomlinson, Homer A. (Box 75, Folder 3505)
  - Torbertt, William (Box 75, Folder 3506)
  - Torrence, Robert G. (Box 75, Folder 3507)
  - Torrey (Bixler), Elizabeth S. (Box 75, Folder 3508)
  - Toti, Robert A. (Box 75, Folder 3509)
  - Tower, Lindsay (Box 75, Folder 3510)
  - Townsend, Ed (Box 75, Folder 3511)
  - Townsend, Howard H., Sr. (Box 75, Folder 3512)
  - Traber, Tony (Box 75, Folder 3513)
  - Tracey, Joshua I. (Box 75, Folder 3514)
  - Treffers, Henry P. (Box 75, Folder 3515)
  - Trent-Lyon, Theodore A. (Box 75, Folder 3516)
  - Tresselt, James F. (Box 75, Folder 3517)
  - Tresselt, Thomas F. (Box 75, Folder 3518)
  - Triffin, Robert (Box 75, Folder 3519)
  - Trilling, L. (Box 75, Folder 3520)
  - Trinkaus, John P. (Box 75, Folder 3521)
  - Trippe, Juan T. (Box 75, Folder 3522)
  - Troutman, Warren T. (Box 75, Folder 3523)
  - Trudeau, Pierre (Box 75, Folder 3524)
  - Truelson, Stanley D. (Box 75, Folder 3525)
  - Truslow, Benoni J. (Box 75, Folder 3526)
  - Tsuneishi, William (Box 75, Folder 3527)
  - Tucker, Ralph B. (Box 75, Folder 3528)
  - Tufts, Sonny (Box 75, Folder 3529)
  - Tuichin, Joseph (Box 75, Folder 3530)
  - Tunnard, Christopher (Box 75, Folder 3531)
  - Tunney, John V. (Box 75, Folder 3532)
  - Turekian, Karl K. (Box 75, Folder 3533)
  - Turkevich, Anthony (Box 75, Folder 3534)
  - Turner, Arthur N. (Box 75, Folder 3535)
  - Turner, Henry A., Jr. (Box 75, Folder 3536)
  - Turner, Hubert M. (Box 75, Folder 3537)
  - Turner, Ralph E. (Box 75, Folder 3538)
  - Tuteur, Frank (Box 75, Folder 3539)
  - Tuttle, A. A. (Box 75, Folder 3540)
  - Tuttle, Emerson (Box 75, Folder 3541)
  - Tworkov, Jack (Box 75, Folder 3542)
  - Tydings, Joseph (Box 75, Folder 3543)
  - Ucello, Ann (Box 76, Folder 3544)
  - Udy, Stanley H., Jr. (Box 76, Folder 3545)
  - Umin, Steve (Box 76, Folder 3546)
  - Underwood, Dale S. (Box 76, Folder 3547)
  - Underwood, Richard (Box 76, Folder 3548)
  - Unruh, Jesse (Box 76, Folder 3549)
  - Uphaus, Willard (Box 76, Folder 3550)
  - Upton, Joe (Box 76, Folder 3551)
  - Usher, Theron, Jr. (Box 76, Folder 3552)
  - U Thant (Box 76, Folder 3553)
  - Vache, Jean E. (Box 76, Folder 3554)
  - Vaill, George D. (Box 76, Folder 3555)
  - Valenti, J. J. (Box 76, Folder 3556)
  - Valentine, Alan (Box 76, Folder 3557)
  - Valentine, Jean (Box 76, Folder 3558)
  - Valpone, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3559)
  - Vance, Cyrus R. (Box 76, Folder 3560)
  - Vance, Eugene A. (Box 76, Folder 3561)
  - Vance, John (Box 76, Folder 3562)
  - Vance, W. R. (Box 76, Folder 3563)
  - Vancisin, Joseph R. (Box 76, Folder 3564)
  - Van de Graaff, Robert J. (Box 76, Folder 3565)
  - Van der Rohe (Box 76, Folder 3566)
  - Van Dyke, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3567)
  - Vannorsdall, John W. (Box 76, Folder 3568)
  - Van Sanford, George (Box 76, Folder 3569)
  - Van Standen, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3570)
  - Van Vechten, Carl (Box 76, Folder 3571)
  - Van Wagenen, Gertrude (Box 76, Folder 3572)
  - Vars, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3573)
  - Vasiliev, Alexander Nicholas (?) (Box 76, Folder 3574)
  - Vaus, James (Box 76, Folder 3575)
  - Velikovsky, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3576)
  - Velimirovic, Milos M. (Box 76, Folder 3577)
  - Verleger, Philip (Box 76, Folder 3578)
  - Vernadsky, George (Box 76, Folder 3579)
  - Veronis, George (Box 76, Folder 3580)
  - Veto, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3581)
  - Videro, Finn (Box 76, Folder 3582)
  - Vieth, Paul H. (Box 76, Folder 3583)
  - Vietor, Alexander O. (Box 76, Folder 3584)
  - Viets, Wallace (Box 76, Folder 3585)
  - Vining, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3586)
  - Vishniac, Wolf (Box 76, Folder 3587)
  - Voigt, Garth K. (Box 76, Folder 3588)
  - Volkart, Edmund H. (Box 76, Folder 3589)
  - Volpe, John (Box 76, Folder 3590)
  - Von Braum, Sigmund (Box 76, Folder 3591)
  - Von Faber du Faur, Curt (Box 76, Folder 3592)
  - Von Staden, Heinrich (Box 76, Folder 3593)
  - Vorys, John Martin (Box 76, Folder 3594)
  - Vostrensenkaya, ----- (Box 76, Folder 3595)
  - Vreeland, Robert P. (Box 76, Folder 3596)
  - Vroom, Victor H. (Box 76, Folder 3597)
  - Waage, Karl M. (Box 76, Folder 3598)
  - Wadsworth, James (Box 76, Folder 3599)
  - Waggoner, Paul E. (Box 76, Folder 3600)
  - Wagner, Allan R. (Box 76, Folder 3601)
  - Wagner, Christian N. J. (Box 76, Folder 3602)
  - Wagner, Robert (Box 76, Folder 3603)
  - Waite, William G. (Box 77, Folder 3604)
  - Waith, Eugene (Box 77, Folder 3605)
  - Wakemann, Edward T. (Box 77, Folder 3606)
  - Waksman, Byron H. (Box 77, Folder 3607)
  - Wald, Florence Schorske (Box 77, Folder 3608)
  - Walker, Charles Allan (Box 77, Folder 3609)
  - Walker, Charles Rumford (Box 77, Folder 3610)
  - Walker, Christopher W. (Box 77, Folder 3611)
  - Walker, Daniel A. (Box 77, Folder 3612)
  - Walker, David M. (Box 77, Folder 3613)
  - Walker, Donald K. (Box 77, Folder 3614)
  - Walker, George H., Jr. (Box 77, Folder 3615)
  - Walker, James C. (Box 77, Folder 3616)
  - Walker, Wyatt Tee (Box 77, Folder 3617)
  - Wallace, George (Box 77, Folder 3618)
  - Wallenius, K. T. (Box 77, Folder 3619)
  - Wallich, Henry (Box 77, Folder 3620)
  - Walling, ----- (Box 77, Folder 3621)
  - Walsh, Jack R. (Box 77, Folder 3622)
  - Walther, John (Box 77, Folder 3623)
  - Walton, Matt S., Jr. (Box 77, Folder 3624)
  - Wandycz, Piotr S. (Box 77, Folder 3625)
  - Wang, Jui Hsin (Box 77, Folder 3626)
  - Wangaad, Frederick F. (Box 77, Folder 3627)
  - Warch, Richard (Box 77, Folder 3628)
  - Ward, Benjamin F. (Box 77, Folder 3629)
  - Ward, R. D. (Box 77, Folder 3630)
  - Wardwell, Edward R. (Box 77, Folder 3631)
  - Warner, Dennis K. (Box 77, Folder 3632)
  - Warner, Richard F. (Box 77, Folder 3633)
  - Wanock, Robert (Box 77, Folder 3634)
  - Warren, David L. (Box 77, Folder 3635)
  - Warren, Richard, Jr. (Box 77, Folder 3636)
  - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 77, Folder 3637)
  - Warshaw, Joseph E. (Box 77, Folder 3638)
  - Washburn, Albert L. (Box 77, Folder 3639)
  - Washinton, George (Box 77, Folder 3640)
  - Wassen, J. Alton, Jr. (Box 77, Folder 3641)
  - Wasserman, Elga R. (Box 77, Folder 3642)
  - Wasserman, Harry H. (Box 78, Folder 3643)
  - Waterhouse, Ellis (Sir) (Box 78, Folder 3644)
  - Waterman, Talbot H. (Box 78, Folder 3645)
  - Waters, Everett O. (Box 78, Folder 3646)
  - Waters, Levin L. (Box 78, Folder 3647)
  - Watkins, Frederick M. (Box 78, Folder 3648)
  - Watson, Arthur K. (Box 78, Folder 3649)
  - Watson, Charles III (Box 78, Folder 3650)
  - Watson, Theodore S. (Box 78, Folder 3651)
  - Watson, William B. (Box 78, Folder 3652)
  - Watson, William W. (Box 78, Folder 3653)
  - Wayne, John (Box 78, Folder 3654)
  - Weaver, Howard Sayer (Box 78, Folder 3655)
  - Webster, Noah (Box 78, Folder 3656)
  - Wechsler, James A. (Box 78, Folder 3657)
  - Wedemeyer, Alfred (Box 78, Folder 3658)
  - Wedge, Bryant M. (Box 78, Folder 3659)
  - Weed, Louis Hill (Box 78, Folder 3660)
  - Wegener, Peter P. (Box 78, Folder 3661)
  - Weh, ----- (Box 78, Folder 3662)
  - Weigand, Hermann J. (Box 78, Folder 3663)
  - Weigel, Timothy (Box 78, Folder 3664)
  - Weigle, Luther A. (Box 78, Folder 3665)
  - Weiner, Norbert (Box 78, Folder 3666)
  - Weiner, Peter (Box 78, Folder 3667)
  - Weinerman, E. Richard (Box 78, Folder 3668)
  - Weinman, David II (Box 78, Folder 3669)
  - Weis, Charles McC. (Box 78, Folder 3670)
  - Weisel, Elie (Box 78, Folder 3671)
  - Weiss, Paul (Box 78, Folder 3672)
  - Weisskopf, Victor F. (Box 78, Folder 3673)
  - Welch, Arnold D. (Box 78, Folder 3674)
  - Welch, Claude (Box 78, Folder 3675)
  - Welch, Constance (Box 78, Folder 3676)
  - Welch, Lewis S. (Box 78, Folder 3677)
  - Welch, Wilford H. (Box 78, Folder 3678)
  - Welleck, Rene (Box 78, Folder 3679)
  - Wellington, Harry H. (Box 79, Folder 3680)
  - Wells, C. Bradford (Box 79, Folder 3681)
  - Wells, M. Henry, Jr. (Box 79, Folder 3682)
  - Wells, Rulon S., III (Box 79, Folder 3683)
  - Welsh, Alexander (Box 79, Folder 3684)
  - Welsh, Robert (Box 79, Folder 3685)
  - Weltner, Charles (Box 79, Folder 3686)
  - Werner-Mueller, Otto (Box 79, Folder 3687)
  - Wesselink, Adriaan J. (Box 79, Folder 3688)
  - Wessin, Y. Wessin (Box 79, Folder 3689)
  - West, Robert L. (Box 79, Folder 3690)
  - Westerfield, H. Bradford (Box 79, Folder 3691)
  - Westerfield, Ray B. (Box 79, Folder 3692)
  - Westheimer, ----- (Box 79, Folder 3693)
  - Westlund, Joseph (Box 79, Folder 3694)
  - Westphal, Merold E. (Box 79, Folder 3695)
  - Whang, Francis M. (Box 79, Folder 3696)
  - Wheeler, Robert G. (Box 79, Folder 3697)
  - Wheeler, Stanton (Box 79, Folder 3698)
  - Wheelock, Keith (Box 79, Folder 3699)
  - Wheelwright, ----- (Box 79, Folder 3700)
  - White, Augustus A., III (Box 79, Folder 3701)
  - White, Constance (Box 79, Folder 3702)
  - White, Zebulon W. (Box 79, Folder 3703)
  - Whitelaw, Maynard W. (Box 79, Folder 3704)
  - Whiteman, Harold B., Jr. (Box 79, Folder 3705)
  - Whiting, Allen (Box 79, Folder 3706)
  - Whitman, Loring (Box 79, Folder 3707)
  - Whitmore, John K. (Box 79, Folder 3708)
  - Whitney, ----- (Box 79, Folder 3709)
  - Whitney, Eli (Box 79, Folder 3710)
  - Whitney, John Hay (Box 79, Folder 3711)
  - Wiberg, Kenneth (Box 79, Folder 3712)
  - Wicker, Tom (Box 79, Folder 3713)
  - Widdoes, Kathleen (Box 79, Folder 3714)
  - Wiedenbach, Ernestine (Box 79, Folder 3715)
  - Wiedersheim, William A. (Box 79, Folder 3716)
  - Wiedmann, Milton L. (Box 79, Folder 3717)
  - Wieland, George R. (Box 79, Folder 3718)
  - Wiens, Herold J. (Box 79, Folder 3719)
  - Wiezbiauski, ----- (Box 79, Folder 3720)
  - Wiggin, Lewis M. (Box 79, Folder 3721)
  - Wilbur, John S. (Box 79, Folder 3722)
  - Wilbur, Richard (Box 79, Folder 3723)
  - Wild, John D. (Box 79, Folder 3724)
  - Wilder, Amos N. (Box 79, Folder 3725)
  - Wilder, A. Tappan (Box 80, Folder 3726)
  - Wildt, Rupert (Box 80, Folder 3727)
  - Wilhelm, Robert (Box 80, Folder 3728)
  - Wilhelmi, Alfred E. (Box 80, Folder 3729)
  - Wilkinson, Denys H. (Box 80, Folder 3730)
  - Wilkinson, John A. (Box 80, Folder 3731)
  - Wilkof, ----- (Box 80, Folder 3732)
  - Will, Robert E. (Box 80, Folder 3733)
  - Willard, William R. (Box 80, Folder 3734)
  - Willcox, William B. (Box 80, Folder 3735)
  - Williams, Colin W. (Box 80, Folder 3736)
  - Williams, Donald R. (Box 80, Folder 3737)
  - Williams, Edward B. (Box 80, Folder 3738)
  - Williams, Elisha (Box 80, Folder 3739)
  - Williams, Frank O. H. (Box 80, Folder 3740)
  - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 80, Folder 3741)
  - Williams, George F. (Box 80, Folder 3742)
  - Williams, Joseph Hill (Box 80, Folder 3743)
  - Williams, Kimbell M. (Box 80, Folder 3744)
  - Williams, Lee (Box 80, Folder 3745)
  - Williams, Robley C., Jr. (Box 80, Folder 3746)
  - Williams, Charles L. (Box 80, Folder 3747)
  - Willis, William J. (Box 80, Folder 3748)
  - Willoughby, Charles L. (Box 80, Folder 3749)
  - Willsey, Carter (Box 80, Folder 3750)
  - Wilson, Bob (Box 80, Folder 3751)
  - Wilson, Charles C. (Box 80, Folder 3752)
  - Wilson, Harold (Box 80, Folder 3753)
  - Wilson, Hugh R., Jr. (Box 80, Folder 3754)
  - Wilson, John O. (Box 80, Folder 3755)
  - Wilson, Keith L. (Box 80, Folder 3756)
  - Wison, Robert (Box 80, Folder 3757)
  - Wimsatt, William K., Jr. (Box 80, Folder 3758)
  - Winchell, Horace (Box 80, Folder 3759)
  - Winer, Herbert (Box 80, Folder 3760)
  - Winerman, Richard E. (Box 80, Folder 3761)
  - Wing, Donald G. (Box 80, Folder 3762)
  - Winks, Robin W. (Box 80, Folder 3763)
  - Winn, James A. (Box 80, Folder 3764)
  - Winslow, Charles Edward A. (Box 80, Folder 3765)
  - Winston, ----- (Box 81, Folder 3766)
  - Winternitz, Milton C. (Box 81, Folder 3767)
  - Wintner, Claude (Box 81, Folder 3768)
  - Wirtz, Willard (Box 81, Folder 3769)
  - Wiston, John (Box 81, Folder 3770)
  - Witherspoon, Alexander (Box 81, Folder 3771)
  - Wittenborn, John R. (Box 81, Folder 3772)
  - Wittfogel (Box 81, Folder 3773)
  - Wizner, Rachel (Box 81, Folder 3774)
  - Wofford, Harris (Box 81, Folder 3775)
  - Wogrin, Conrad A. (Box 81, Folder 3776)
  - Wohlenberg, Ernest T. F. (Box 81, Folder 3777)
  - Wohlenberg, Walter J. (Box 81, Folder 3778)
  - Wolf, Arnold Jacob (Box 81, Folder 3779)
  - Wolf, Gerrit (Box 81, Folder 3780)
  - Wolf, Merril K. (Box 81, Folder 3781)
  - Wolf, Tom (Box 81, Folder 3782)
  - Wolf, Werner Paul (Box 81, Folder 3783)
  - Wolfer, John A. (Box 81, Folder 3784)
  - Wolfers, Arnold (Box 81, Folder 3785)
  - Wolfgang, Richard L. (Box 81, Folder 3786)
  - Wondriska, William (Box 81, Folder 3787)
  - Wood, ----- (Box 81, Folder 3788)
  - Wood, Peggy (Box 81, Folder 3789)
  - Woodcock, Leonard (Box 81, Folder 3790)
  - Woodhouse, Edward J. (Box 81, Folder 3791)
  - Woodruff, Robert M. (Box 81, Folder 3792)
  - Woodward, C. Van (Box 81, Folder 3793)
  - Woodward, Ralph L. (Box 81, Folder 3794)
  - Woolsey, Theodore (Box 81, Folder 3795)
  - Worrell, Albert C. (Box 81, Folder 3796)
  - Worth, Irene (Box 81, Folder 3797)
  - Worth, William (Box 81, Folder 3798)
  - Wright, ----- (Box 81, Folder 3799)
  - Wright, Arthur F. (Box 81, Folder 3800)
  - Wright, Mary (Box 81, Folder 3801)
  - Wu, King Lui (Box 81, Folder 3802)
  - Wu, Nelson I. (Box 81, Folder 3803)
  - Wyatt, Gerard R. (Box 81, Folder 3804)
  - Wynn, F. Houston (Box 81, Folder 3805)
  - Yale, David (Box 81, Folder 3806)
  - Yale, Elihu (Box 81, Folder 3807)
  - Yamaga, Chitoshi (Box 81, Folder 3808)
  - Yarborough, Ralph (Box 81, Folder 3809)
  - Yarmolinsky, Adam (Box 82, Folder 3810)
  - Yates, Douglas T. (Box 82, Folder 3811)
  - Yeh, ----- (Box 82, Folder 3812)
  - Yelon, Arthur M. (Box 82, Folder 3813)
  - York, Lewis E. (Box 82, Folder 3814)
  - Young, Dana (Box 82, Folder 3815)
  - Young, Philip Taylor, Jr. (Box 82, Folder 3816)
  - Young, Whitney (Box 82, Folder 3817)
  - Yovicsin, John M. (Box 82, Folder 3818)
  - Zaeder, J. Philip (Box 82, Folder 3819)
  - Zallinger, Rudolph F. (Box 82, Folder 3820)
  - Zauchenberger, Herwig (Box 82, Folder 3821)
  - Zeckendor, F. William (Box 82, Folder 3822)
  - Zeleny, John (Box 82, Folder 3823)
  - Zellner, Bob (Box 82, Folder 3824)
  - Zigler, Edward F. (Box 82, Folder 3825)
  - Zinsser, William K. (Box 82, Folder 3826)
  - Ziolkowski, Theodore J. (Box 82, Folder 3827)
  - Zucker, Bernard (Box 82, Folder 3828)
  - Zuckerman, Albert J. (Box 82, Folder 3829)
  - Zuckerman, Bernard D. (Box 82, Folder 3930)
  - Zuckert, Eugene (Box 82, Folder 3831)
  - Zuckenburg, ----- (Box 82, Folder 3832)
  - Zumwalt, Eugene V. (Box 82, Folder 3833)
  - Zweig, Feliz (Box 82, Folder 3834)
- Photographs of individuals, 1973-1995; Series II
  - Abramovitz, Robert (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Addison, Clara (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Ahlstrom, Sydney E. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Aissen, Judith (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Aldrich, Richard W. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Alderfer, Clayton P. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Elizabeth C. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, Rev. Dwight (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Angell, Katharine (Mrs. James Rowland Angell) (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Andriole, Vincent T. (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Ariyan, Stephen (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Armstrong, John E. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Arterton, F. Christopher (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Astrachan, Boris M. (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Avitable, Marie (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Bainton, Roland H. (The Rev.) (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Baker, Mark L. (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Bandelin, Carl (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Barghoorn, Frederick (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Barrnett, Russell J. (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Baue, Arthur E. (M.D.) (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Batchelor, C. Malcolm (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Baumer, Franklin L. (Box 83, Folder 23)